{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090053147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090053147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zo_za_zu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090059765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090059765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zu_za_zo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090066392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090066391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zu_za_zo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090073052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090073052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_zo_zi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090080512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090080512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_zo_zi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090087138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090087138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_za_zu_zo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090093783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090093783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zo_zu_ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090100434","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090100433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_zi_zo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090107902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090107901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_zi_zo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090114579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090114579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_zu_za"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090122038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090122038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_zu_za"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090132156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090132155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ze_zu_za"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090138800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090138800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zu_za_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090139852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090139852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" bc2cb32d-7d7a-4739-a6fc-7923975b2aad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_zu_za_zo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090148470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090148470"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" 03be7dd0-08a2-47f8-8610-25d2b85b1489"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090148701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090148701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" 03be7dd0-08a2-47f8-8610-25d2b85b1489"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090149328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090149328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" 03be7dd0-08a2-47f8-8610-25d2b85b1489"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090163758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090163758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090163991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090163991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090164965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090164965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090166242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090166242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090169214","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090169214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090170072","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090170072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090170397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090170396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090171642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090171642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090175227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090175226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090176223","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090176223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090176488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090176488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090177446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090177446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090180362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090180361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090181405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090181405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090181885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090181885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090184097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090184096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090184198","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090184198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" d5ce1cb3-cedb-4859-b9ef-5070d612a5bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090204446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090204446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" e28cb75b-8bfb-4ab7-bb57-e1a090e732b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zo_za_zu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549090211115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549090211115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_094706"," gameId":" e28cb75b-8bfb-4ab7-bb57-e1a090e732b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.zo..zo.noShow..13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zu_za_zo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}